## Pitchayakit Pahamak Software Engineer

Last update: April 12, 2024

The online version is available at

https://pitchayakit.github.io/cv

Residence	Bangkok, Thailand
Phone	<u>+66831225471</u>
GitHub	• pitchayakit
Email	☑ <u>pitchayakit.p@gmail.com</u>

NodeJs	+++++	ExpressJs	+++++	Laravel	+++++	PHP	++++	CSS	+++++	SQL	++++
Livewire	++++	AlpineJs	++++	jQuery	++++	Tailwind	++++	Bootstrap	++++	WordPress	++++
Restful	++++	GIT	++++	VueJs	+++	Linux	+++	Nginx	+++	Python	++

With over 7 years of experience in the software development industry, I have honed my skills in a diverse range of companies, including startups and digital agencies. My expertise spans all aspects of the software development lifecycle and project management. I have a particular passion for Internet of Things (IoT) and Machine Learning technologies, and am always seeking ways to leverage these to enhance everyday life.

## **Professional Experience**

#### Rocket 8

May 2023 - Present

- Collaborating with product development and design team
- · Creating a Document (SSOT) for a development team
- Design User Journey, User Flow, Code pattern, Review code
- · Research state of the art
- Design database schema
- · Data migration from legacy system to new system
- Writing clean, testable, high-quality code
- Upgrade and maintain web applications and database for maximum performance



#### Lexicon

Aug 2020 - Apr 2023

- Maintained web servers and managed CI/CD processes
- Developed clean, testable, and high-quality code
- Managed the Line CRM system
- Managed a CMS using Laravel, Nova, and WordPress
- · Implemented and managed Elasticsearch
- · Handled data migration tasks
- Mentored junior developers in web development and provided technical support



#### Freelancer

2018 - 2020

- Managed company, e-commerce, and library websites
- Upgraded and maintained web applications for optimal performance
- Collaborated closely with stakeholders to understand their unique requirements and goals

| WordPress | Laravel

#### **Empag**

Oct 2017 - Oct 2018

- · Coached interns in web development and provided technical support
- Managed web content management systems and collaborated with video and content teams to gather requirements and implement solutions
- Collaborated with designers to ensure the quality and accuracy of designs
- Developed a tool for web scraping and exporting data to Excel files

WordPress | NodeJs

#### Onestockhome

Mar 2017 - Sep 2017

- Migrated content management system to Ruby on Rails platform
- Developed front-end of website using jQuery, Bootstrap, HTML, and CSS in Ruby on Rails platform
- Supported the use of content management system and improved user interface

Ruby on Rail React

### Rippleworkz

2016 - 2017

- Integrated HTML with WordPress and Prestashop
- · Managed web content management systems and multitasked effectively
- · Collaborated with project manager to develop websites beyond own project scope

| WordPress | jQuery |

# SeSaMe (Sensor-enhanced Social Media) Center, National University of Singapore

Jul 2015 - Dec 2015

- SENSE video analytics web application replaced video output for detection, tracking and counting by HTML Canvas
- Take over and developed SeSaMe website using Joomla CMS

Play Framework HTML Canvas Joomla OpenCV MongoDB

#### Education

Master of Network Learning Technology, College of Electrical Engineering & Computer Science, National Central University, Taiwan [2018 - 2020]

Bachelor of Computer Engineering, College of Engineering, Kasetsart University, Thailand [2013 - 2016]

## Additional Experience

A Study of using IoT and Zenbo robot to facilitate students' interaction in flipped classroom and the analysis of their perception.

IoT Zenbo Machine learning

Smart home with door and light control system.

IoT PHP JQuery